Guide to the Isidore Sydney Falk Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Professional Activities, 1919-1979; Series II; 44 linear feet (107 boxes)
  - Yale University, Department of Epidemiology and Public Health
    - Course Materials, Post 1968
      - Department of Epidemiology and Public Health
        - Introduction to Health Services 170A: outline, correspondence, and background material, 1971 November-1972 January (Box 125, Folder 1709)
        - Case Studies in Health Administration: outline, correspondence and background material, 1972 September-October (Box 125, Folder 1710)
        - Social Medicine 110A: schedule, reading list and correspondence, 1972 (Box 125, Folder 1711)
        - Medical Care in the United States 171B: notes, schedule and correspondence, 1972 December-1973 May 7 (Box 125, Folder 1712)
        - Social Medicine 110A
          - Schedule and background material, 1973 September 6-December 6 (Box 125, Folder 1713)
          - Lectures 6-7: outline and notes, 1973 October (Box 125, Folder 1714)
        - Introduction to Health Services 170A
          - Schedule and correspondence, 1974 October-December (Box 125, Folder 1715)
          - Lecture 3: outline and notes, 1974 November 4 (Box 125, Folder 1716)
        - Case Studies in Health Administration 273A: correspondence, 1975 January-February (Box 125, Folder 1717)
        - Health Services Administration 170: outline, notes and background material, 1975 December 1 (Box 125, Folder 1718)
        - Case Studies in Health Services 273B
          - Schedule, reading list and correspondence, 1976 January-May (Box 125, Folder 1719)
          - Lecture 12: background material, 1976 April 13 (Box 126, Folder 1720)
        - Sociology of Health Care 275B
          - Schedule and correspondence, 1976 January-May (Box 126, Folder 1721)
          - Lecture 13: outline, notes and background material, 1976 April 20 (Box 126, Folder 1722)
        - Ambulatory Health Services 297B: schedule, reading list and correspondence, 1976 January-May (Box 126, Folder 1723)
        - Introduction to Health Services 170A
          - Correspondence, 1976 July (Box 126, Folder 1724)
          - Schedule and correspondence, 1977 September-December (Box 126, Folder 1725)
          - Lecture 18: outline and background material, 1977 December 19 (Box 126, Folder 1726)
        - Health Services Administration 570A: schedule, correspondence and reading list, 1978 September-December (Box 126, Folder 1727)
        - Health Services Administration 697A: schedule, reading list and correspondence, 1978 September-December (Box 126, Folder 1728)
        - Ambulatory Health Services 297B: correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 1729)
        - Health Services Administration 697A
          - Outline, notes and background material, 1979 October 24 (Box 126, Folder 1730)
          - Correspondence and outline, 1980 March-October (Box 126, Folder 1731)
      - Economics Department, "The Medical Care Industry in the U.S.A.": outline, notes and background material, 1965 November 15 (Box 126, Folder 1732)
      - Law School
        - "Social Legislation": outline and background material, 1966 October 24 (Box 126, Folder 1733)
        - "Some History about Medical Care Legislation": outline, 1968 November 7 (Box 126, Folder 1734)
      - School of Organization and Management, "The National H.M.O. Program and Its Significance for National Health Insurance": outline and notes, 1978 November 1 (Box 126, Folder 1735)
    - Project Files
      - Yale-New Haven Medical Center
        - Background material, 1952-1960 (Box 126, Folder 1736)
        - Final report, 1960 July 12 (Box 126, Folder 1737)
        - Reports, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 1738)
        - Print material, 1961-1968 (Box 126, Folder 1739)
        - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 126, Folder 1740)
        - Speech text (Vernon W. Lippard), 1962 April 17 (Box 126, Folder 1741)
        - Reports, 1962-1963, 1966, undated (Box 126, Folder 1742)
        - Conference on Planning of Ambulatory Services
          - Notes (I.S.F.), program and related material, 1963 September 7, 1964 September 19 (Box 126, Folder 1743-1744)
          - Summary report (E.R. Weinerman), 1965 February 5 (Box 126, Folder 1745)
      - Standards for Good Medical Care (I.S.F., J.F. Heston, H.K. Schonfeld)
        - Background material and notes (D. Pearson), 1962 Nov, 1963, October 11 (Box 126, Folder 1746)
        - Correspondence, memoranda and report (I.V. Hiscock), 1962-1963 (Box 126, Folder 1747)
        - Print material re: psychiatric aspects, 1963-1964, undated (Box 126, Folder 1748)
        - Correspondence and notes re: psychiatric aspects, 1963-1966 (Box 127, Folder 1749)
        - Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 127, Folder 1750)
        - Proposal texts, 1966 June-December (Box 127, Folder 1751)
        - Correspondence, 1968-1977 (Box 127, Folder 1752-1753)
        - Text and abstract, Vol. I, 1975 February (Box 127, Folder 1754)
        - Text, Vol. II, 1975 February (Box 127, Folder 1755)
        - Text, Vol. III, 1975 February (Box 127, Folder 1756)
        - Text, Vol. IV, 1975 February (Box 127, Folder 1757)
      - New Haven pretest of the 1970 Census
        - Correspondence, memoranda and notes, Circa 1962-1963, 1966 January-July (Box 127, Folder 1758)
        - Correspondence, memoranda and notes, 1966 August-1967 January (Box 128, Folder 1759)
    - Other Material
      - Yale University, School of Nursing
        - Reports and related material, 1955, 1958-1959 (Box 128, Folder 1760)
        - Print material, 1955-1963 (Box 128, Folder 1761)
        - Correspondence, [1960?]-1962 (Box 128, Folder 1762)
        - Research grant applications and study proposals, 1960-1963 (Box 128, Folder 1763)
        - Reports and related material, 1961-1963 (Box 128, Folder 1764)
      - Speech text, "Supply of Health Care Personnel" (Vernon W. Lippard), 1961 October 3 (Box 128, Folder 1765)
      - Cornell University, Sloan Institute of Hospital Administration
        - Outline and notes, 1962 June 27 (Box 128, Folder 1766)
        - Background material, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 1767)
        - Correspondence and schedule, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 1768)
        - Notes and correspondence, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 1769)
        - Background material, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 1770)
        - Outline and notes, 1964 June 23 (Box 128, Folder 1771)
        - Correspondence and schedule, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 1772)
        - Background material, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 1773)
        - Outline and notes, 1965 July 1 (Box 128, Folder 1774)
        - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 1775)
        - Background material, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 1776)
        - Outline, 1966 June 27 (Box 128, Folder 1777)
        - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 1778)
        - Background material, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 1779)
        - Outline and notes, 1967 June 19 (Box 128, Folder 1780)
        - Background material, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 1781)
        - Outline, 1968 June 17 (Box 128, Folder 1782)
        - Background material, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 1783)
        - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 1784)
        - Correspondence and background material, 1969 (Box 128, Folder 1785)
        - Outline and notes, 1970 June 22 (Box 128, Folder 1786)
        - Correspondence and background material, 1970 (Box 128, Folder 1787)
        - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 129, Folder 1788)
        - Outline, 1974 June 19 (Box 129, Folder 1789)
        - Correspondence and background material, 1974-1975 (Box 129, Folder 1790-1791)
        - Outline, 1976 June 22 (Box 129, Folder 1792)
        - Correspondence and background material, 1976 (Box 129, Folder 1793)
        - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 129, Folder 1794)
      - University of Michigan, Conference on Teaching Medical Care Administration
        - Outline, correspondence and leaflets, 1965 March-June (Box 129, Folder 1795)
        - Draft report, 1965 June 24-26 (Box 129, Folder 1796)
        - Background material, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 1797-1798)
      - Yale University Medical School, Ad Hoc Committee on Education
        - Draft report, 1965 November 30 (Box 129, Folder 1799)
        - Correspondence and related material, 1965-1967 (Box 129, Folder 1800)
        - Report, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 1801)
      - Discussion text re: hospital plan for New York City (E. Cohart, I.S.F., J.C. Oakley, A. Snoke, J.D. Thompson), 1967 May 26 (Box 129, Folder 1802)
      - Notes and outline re: grant for a Health Service Research Center (I.S.F., H.K. Schonfeld), 1967 November (Box 129, Folder 1803)
      - New England Commissioners' Institute on Medical Care Administration
        - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 129, Folder 1804)
        - Outline and text, 1968 April 8 (Box 129, Folder 1805)
        - Schedules, 1968 April 8-10 (Box 129, Folder 1806)
        - Background material, 1968 (Box 129, Folder 1807)
      - Correspondence and print material re: "Medicine and the Social Sciences", 1972 September-November (Box 129, Folder 1808)
  - Community Health Care Center Plan, Inc.
    - Correspondence
      - General, A-Y, 1966-1979 (Box 129, Folder 1809)
      - Block, James, 1967-1968 (Box 129, Folder 1810)
      - Bondy, Philip K., 1965-1967 (Box 129, Folder 1811)
      - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1968-1970 (Box 129, Folder 1812)
      - Commission on Hospitals and Health Care of Connecticut, 1974-1977 (Box 129, Folder 1813)
      - Connecticut State Medical Society, Connecticut Ambulatory Care Study, 1972-1973 (Box 130, Folder 1814)
      - Dearing, W. Palmer, 1966-1969 (Box 130, Folder 1815)
      - Driscoll, John J., 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1816)
      - Glasser, Melvin, 1968-1978 (Box 130, Folder 1817)
      - Grasso, Ella T., 1975 (Box 130, Folder 1818)
      - Greenberg, Ruth W., 1966-1971 (Box 130, Folder 1819)
      - Health Insurance Plan of Greater New York, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 130, Folder 1820)
      - Lee, Richard C., 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1821)
      - Lippard, Vernon W., 1965-1967 (Box 130, Folder 1822)
      - MacLeod, Gordon K., 1966-1967 (Box 130, Folder 1823)
      - Maher, Edward W., 1975 (Box 130, Folder 1824)
      - Meany, George, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1825)
      - Merriam, Ida C., 1966 (Box 130, Folder 1826)
      - Morrison, James F., 1975 (Box 130, Folder 1827)
      - Nelson, John A., 1969 (Box 130, Folder 1828)
      - New Haven County Medical Association, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1829)
      - Redlich, Fredrick C., 1968 (Box 130, Folder 1830)
      - Schaffer, Gloria, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 1831)
      - Shapiro, Bernard, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1832)
      - Sirabella, Vincent J., 1967-1968 (Box 130, Folder 1833)
      - Snoke, Albert W., 1965-1966 (Box 130, Folder 1834)
      - United States Civil Service Commission, 1971 (Box 130, Folder 1835)
      - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare
        - General, 1967-1971 (Box 130, Folder 1836)
        - Cohen, Wilbur J., 1967-1968 (Box 130, Folder 1837)
        - Cowhig, James D., 1966-1969 (Box 130, Folder 1838)
        - Flook, Evelyn, 1963-1974 (Box 130, Folder 1839)
        - Griffiths, Robert E., 1969-1972 (Box 130, Folder 1840)
        - McKee, Frank W., 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1841)
        - Manegold, Richard F., 1967-1968 (Box 130, Folder 1842)
        - Mathewson, Herbert O., 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1843)
        - Regional Office (I), 1968-1974 (Box 130, Folder 1844)
        - Rikli, Arthur E., 1966-1967 (Box 130, Folder 1845)
        - Silver, George A., 1968 (Box 130, Folder 1846)
        - West, Howard, 1967-1974 (Box 130, Folder 1847)
        - Zusman, Jack, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1848)
      - United States Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1966 (Box 130, Folder 1849)
      - United Steelworkers of America, 1968-1972 (Box 130, Folder 1850)
    - Planning and Development Papers
      - Affiliation agreement with Yale-New Haven Medical Center and related material, 1960-1969 (Box 130, Folder 1851)
      - Reprints re: labor unions and medical care (I.S.F.), 1963-1966 (Box 130, Folder 1852)
      - Reports on other health maintenance organizations and projections of necessary services, 1965-1970 (Box 130, Folder 1853)
      - Memoranda, reports, minutes, 1965-1969 (Box 131, Folder 1854)
      - Certification of incorporation, bylaws and related material, 1966-1969 (Box 131, Folder 1855)
      - Correspondence re: staff recruitment, 1966-1969 (Box 131, Folder 1856)
      - Press releases, 1967-1969 (Box 131, Folder 1857)
      - Notes (I.S.F.) and related material re: radio broadcast, 1967 April (Box 131, Folder 1858)
      - Staff reports on aspects of setting up a community health care center and memorandum re: scope of benefits, 1967-1969, 1970 (Box 131, Folder 1859)
      - Legislation
        - "An Act Incorporating Community Health Care Center Plan, Inc." (S. B. 1711)
          - Correspondence re: Connecticut State Labor Council and Greater New Haven Central Labor Council, 1966-1968 (Box 131, Folder 1860)
          - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 131, Folder 1861)
          - Correspondence and notes re: meeting with Connecticut State Medical Society (I.S.F.), 1967 (Box 131, Folder 1862)
          - Drafts of text and related material, 1967 (Box 131, Folder 1863)
          - History of Special Act 335, Circa 1967 (Box 131, Folder 1864)
          - Testimony of Robert K. Match and Gordon K. MacLeod, 1967 April 18 (Box 131, Folder 1865)
        - Newsclippings re: attitudes towards New Haven Health Center, 1967-1968 (Box 131, Folder 1866)
        - "An Act Concerning Nonprofit Health Care Centers" (bill no. 7583): correspondence, drafts of bill and notes (I.S.F.), 1969 (Box 131, Folder 1867)
        - "An Act Concerning Council on Hospitals," (H. B. 5164): notes (I.S.F.) and drafts of amendment to bill (Box 131, Folder 1868)
        - "An Act Creating a Commission on Hospitals and Health Care" (H. B. 8920): suggested changes, notes (I.S.F.) and substitute bill, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 1869)
    - Grants and Contracts
      - Survey of medical care available to union members in Connecticut: report to Connecticut State Labor Council (I.S.F), 1964 June 11 (Box 131, Folder 1870)
      - "Studies on the planning of a community program for comprehensive family care through group practice in a teaching medical center setting"
        - Correspondence, project plans and agreements for funding, 1966 (Box 131, Folder 1871)
        - Correspondence re: use of U.S. Census study as a research tool for grant (G.K. MacLeod), 1967 (Box 131, Folder 1872)
        - Progress reports 2, 3, 4 and supplemental material, 1967 (Box 131, Folder 1873)
        - Progress reports 5, 6 and supplemental material, 1968 (Box 131, Folder 1874)
        - Progress reports 7, 8 and supplemental material, 1968 (Box 131, Folder 1875)
        - Progress reports 9, 10, 11 and supplemental material, 1969 (Box 131, Folder 1876)
        - Draft of final report and supplemental material, 1969-1970 (Box 132, Folder 1877)
      - "The Community Program for Prepaid Family Health Care"
        - Correspondence re: tax exempt status for Community Health Center Plan, 1968-1970 (Box 132, Folder 1878)
        - Correspondence with Kellogg Foundation re: financial assistance, 1968-1969 (Box 132, Folder 1879)
        - Draft of grant application and related tabulations, 1968 April (Box 132, Folder 1880)
        - Memoranda re: changes in application and prospectus on the research program, 1968 June-July (Box 132, Folder 1881)
        - Survey forms used to test attitudes of low-income households and labor-union members, 1968 July (Box 132, Folder 1882)
        - Grant application with appendices, 1968 May (Box 132, Folder 1883)
        - Grant application with revised budget tables, 1968 September-December (Box 132, Folder 1884)
        - Correspondence, grant excerpts, budget tables and charts, 1969 January (Box 132, Folder 1885)
        - Correspondence and project summaries, 1969 February-August (Box 132, Folder 1886)
        - Progress report and speech text, 1969-1971 (Box 133, Folder 1887)
        - Correspondence and narrative description, 1970 July (Box 133, Folder 1888)
        - Final report, 1973 November (Box 133, Folder 1889)
      - "Research and Evaluation of a Community Health Program for Prepaid Family Health Care"
        - Correspondence, application and related material, 1969 March-November (Box 133, Folder 1890)
        - Progress report 1, 2, 1969 November 7-1970 (Box 133, Folder 1891)
        - Progress report 3, 4, 1970 (Box 133, Folder 1892)
        - Progress report 5, 1970 October 23 (Box 133, Folder 1893)
        - Progress report 6, 1971 January 29 (Box 133, Folder 1894)
        - Progress report 7, 1971 March 31 (Box 133, Folder 1895)
        - Progress report 8, 1971 June 30 (Box 133, Folder 1896)
        - Progress report 9, 1972 January-February (Box 134, Folder 1897)
        - Progress report 9, 1972 January 8 (Box 134, Folder 1898)
        - Progress report 10, 1972 December 26 (Box 134, Folder 1899)
      - "The Health Manpower Training Program"
        - Correspondence and related material re: foundation support, 1969-1970 (Box 134, Folder 1900)
        - Correspondence and addenda with Kellogg Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 134, Folder 1901)
      - "Incorporation of Eligibles in the Community Program for Prepaid Family Health Care" (H.M.O. Development Grant): correspondence, application and related material, 1971 (Box 134, Folder 1902)
      - "Research, Demonstrations, and Evaluations in a G.P.P.P."
        - Application, 1972 June (Box 134, Folder 1903)
        - Application appendices, 1972 June (Box 134, Folder 1904)
        - Correspondence and charts, 1972 September (Box 134, Folder 1905)
      - "Utilization and Efficiency of Health Manpower in Health Maintenance Organizations or Prepaid Group Practices": correspondence, drafts of proposal and related material, 1972-1974 (Box 134, Folder 1906)
      - H.M.O. contract for C.H.C.P. in the Connecticut State Welfare Department: correspondence, 1974 June-July (Box 134, Folder 1907)
    - Physical Facility Papers
      - Correspondence and minutes, 1966-1972 (Box 134, Folder 1908)
      - Architect's diagrams, space and staff allocations, 1967-1968 (Box 135, Folder 1909)
      - Architect's rough draft, 1967 September (Box 135, Folder 1910)
      - Costs: correspondence, charts and proposals, 1967-1971 (Box 135, Folder 1911)
      - Site acquisition: correspondence and related material, 1968-1969 (Box 135, Folder 1912)
      - Site acquisition: correspondence, survey map and related material, 1969-1970 (Box 135, Folder 1913)
      - Architectural report, first draft, 1969 May 15 (Box 135, Folder 1914)
      - Architect's report on design of a health care center for D.H.E.W. grant, 1969 October (Box 135, Folder 1915)
      - Correspondence and reports (B.P. Arneil), 1975-1979 (Box 135, Folder 1916)
    - Reports
      - "The First Two Clinical Operational Years of the Community Health Care Center Plan, Inc." (I.S.F.), 1971 October 1-1973 September 30 (Box 135, Folder 1917)
      - Annual Report, 1973-1977 (Box 135, Folder 1918-1919)
      - Report to the Plan's Enrollees, 1976 (Box 136, Folder 1920)
      - Annual Report, 1977-1979 (Box 136, Folder 1921)
      - Report to the Plan's Enrollees, 1977-1979 (Box 136, Folder 1922)
    - Publications
      - "Health Insurance through Collective Bargaining in the New Haven Area" (I.S.F.)
        - Text and abstract, 1965 October 20 (Box 136, Folder 1923)
        - Correspondence re: paper, 1965 (Box 136, Folder 1924)
        - Correspondence re: survey, 1965 (Box 136, Folder 1925)
      - Reprints (I.S.F.), 1966-1969 (Box 136, Folder 1926)
      - "A Community Group Practice Prepayment Plan Linked with the Medical School Center in New Haven, Conn." (I.S.F.), 1969 June (Box 136, Folder 1927)
      - "The Community Health Care Center Plan, Inc.: Some Adventures in the Development of our Prepaid Group Practice Program" (W.D. Paley), 1972 May (Box 136, Folder 1927)
    - Miscellaneous Material
      - Bills, newsclippings and correspondence, 1963-1968 (Box 136, Folder 1929)
      - "Legal Rights of Group Health Plans, A Survey of State Laws Through 1963" (H.R. Hansen): text, 1964 May (Box 136, Folder 1930)
      - Newsclippings, 1964-1979 (Box 136, Folder 1931)
      - Printed matter, 1966-1973 (Box 136, Folder 1932)
- Subject and Organization Files, 1931-1980; Series III; 10 linear feet (25 boxes)
  SUBJECT AND ORGANIZATION FILES is organized in nine sections: American Hospital Association, Hospital Payment Conference, American Public Health Association, American Public Welfare Association, Committee for National Health Insurance, Committee for the Nation's Health, Committee on Research in Medical Economics, Forand Bill and Related Bills, Group Health Association of America, Nonspecific Immunity, and Sturges (Gertrude), Disposition of Estate. The sections are arranged either chronologically or alphabetically depending on the type of material. The longer sections are organized in subsections.
  - American Hospital Association, Hospital Payment Conference
    - Reference material, 1949-1952 (Box 136a, Folder 1933)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 136a, Folder 1934)
    - Program and related material, 1951 May (Box 136a, Folder 1935)
    - Report and comments on conference, 1951 Sep, December (Box 136a, Folder 1936)
    - Progress report, 1953 January (Box 136a, Folder 1937)
  - American Public Health Association
    - Correspondence
      - Atwater, Reginald M., 1944-1957 (Box 137, Folder 1938)
      - Barrett, William A., 1966 (Box 137, Folder 1938)
      - Calver, Homer N., 1930 (Box 137, Folder 1938)
      - Cornely, Paul B., 1968 (Box 137, Folder 1938)
      - Elder, Frank B., 1956 (Box 137, Folder 1939)
      - Emerson, Haven, 1934 (Box 137, Folder 1939)
      - Emerson, Kendall, 1934 (Box 137, Folder 1939)
      - Fry, Marion, 1959 (Box 137, Folder 1939)
      - Hood, Thomas R., 1967-1969 (Box 137, Folder 1940)
      - Kimmey, James R., 1972 (Box 137, Folder 1940)
      - Knutson, John W., 1957 (Box 137, Folder 1940)
      - Lewis, Deborah A., 1976 (Box 137, Folder 1940)
      - Long, Lillian D., 1967 (Box 137, Folder 1941)
      - Mattison, Berwyn F., 1959-1970 (Box 137, Folder 1941)
      - Mickle, Friend Lee, 1931 (Box 137, Folder 1941)
      - Mountin, Joseph W., 1947 (Box 137, Folder 1941)
      - Notkin, Herbert, 1955 (Box 137, Folder 1941)
      - Ravenel, Mazyck P., 1931 (Box 137, Folder 1942)
      - Renthal, A. Gerald, 1967-1968 (Box 137, Folder 1942)
      - Rosen, George, 1960, 1971 (Box 137, Folder 1942)
      - Walker, W. F., 1931 (Box 137, Folder 1942)
      - Walsh, Willimina R., 1959 (Box 137, Folder 1942)
      - Williams, Josephine J., 1959 (Box 137, Folder 1942)
      - Witte, Ernest F., 1959 (Box 137, Folder 1942)
    - Annual Meeting Papers
      - Correspondence and papers, 1948 November 8-11, 1948 November 16-22, 1949-1950 (Box 137, Folder 1943-1947)
      - Address, "Methods of Payment for Physicians Services in Medical Care Programs" (F. Goldmann), 1951 October 31 (Box 137, Folder 1948)
      - Address, "The Use and Abuse of Prepaid Comprehensive Physicians' Services" (S. J. Axelrod, R. E. Patton), 1951 November 1 (Box 137, Folder 1949)
      - Program, 1966-1968 (Box 137, Folder 1950-1952)
      - Abstracts, 1969 (Box 137, Folder 1953)
      - Program, 1969-1970 (Box 137, Folder 1954-1955)
      - Program and abstracts, 1971 (Box 137, Folder 1956)
      - Correspondence and papers, 1974 (Box 137, Folder 1957)
    - Committee and Section Papers
      - Committee on Administrative Practice, Subcommittee on Medical Care
        - Administrative files
          - Correspondence and minutes, 1944 January-Oct, 1945 January-Nov, 1946 February-Nov, 1947 February-Apr, July (Box 137, Folder 1958-1966)